ACWA Education Department Records 5619/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor Bookshelf, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Legal, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Legislative Lists, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Personnel, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Clothing Insurance requests, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- APEC Leaflets, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Dues Requests, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  November1972
- Dues Leaflets, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Materials Published by this Department, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Purchasing, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Research, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Staff Meetings, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Joint Boards, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Scranton- Legislative Conference, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  Location: Washington D.C, Duration: April 9-11
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Local Joint Boards, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Milton Watson, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- South, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Correspondence A to Z, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Voter Registration campaign, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  Front Lash
- Schools and universities, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- AFL- CIO, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous Unions, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Local 189 American Federation of Teachers, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Smithsonian, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Farah Strike, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Paperbacks- Bills Paid, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Paperbacks- Bills Not Paid, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- George Guernsey, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Paperbacks- Advance Orders, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Paperbacks- Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Eastern Summer School, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  August 4-10
- Eastern Summer School, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Southern Legislative Conferences, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Convention Materials and Orders, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Watts Bar Dam School, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Staff Training School, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Location: Pawling, N.Y; Duration: October 28- November 3
- Leadership Training Institute, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Location: El Paso; Duration: April 23-30
- Conferences, Trips, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Congressional District Communications, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Executive, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- National Education Department, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- National Education Department, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Finance, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Visitors, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Foreign Visitors, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- ACWA Ledger, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Inter-Office Memos, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Legal, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Farah Buttons, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Memorial Program, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Convention Union Activities Room, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Credential, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  Textile Union Workers of America
- Convention Committees, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Keynote Address, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Joe Glazer, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Resolutions, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Messages- Paul Waitt, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Convention Follow Up, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Invitations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  Guests, Staff
- Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA) Convention, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Vice President Election Campaign, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Material Published by this Department, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Material Published by this Department, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Form Letters- general, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- William Elkuss- Correspondence, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- William Elkuss- Correspondence, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Material Requests, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Material Published by this Department, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Purchasing, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Reports, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Research, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Staff Management, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Union Label, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Joint Boards B and C, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Pittsburgh Regional Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Milton Watson, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Locals and Joint Boards, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Film correspondence, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Inheritance- Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Inheritance- Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Film Correspondence, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Inheritance- Preview Requests, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Inheritance- Preview Requests, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Inheritance- Purchased by Organization, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Inheritance- Purchased by Organization, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Correspondence A to Z, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- A to Z Correspondence, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Labor Bookshelf, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Senior Josephine Mastandrea, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Cornell University, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Subscriptions, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- University Labor Education Association, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Paperbacks- Bills Paid, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Paperbacks- Advance Orders, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- AFL-CIO, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Miscellaneous ACWU Materials (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Bi County Joint Boards, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Locals- 317-2494-385-1708-1807
- Federation Of Union Representatives (F.O.U.R), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Leaflets, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Plans, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Vastina Wilson
- Pennsylvania Key Stone Joint Board, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Vastina Wilson, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- R.I Roper, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Check Off Membership and Seniority Material, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Brown Lung, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Brown Lungs Blues Newsletter
- Inter Office News Briefs, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Expense Sheets, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Merger Materials, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- IOEU, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Activity Sheets, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Congressional District Committees, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Coalition Of Labor Union Women, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Collective Bargaining Material Speeches, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Films Ordered, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Elections, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Staff Retirement Plan, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Staff Meetings, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Southern States Information, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Textile Industries, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Mill Strike, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  Location: Columbia, South Carolina
- Social Service, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Rentals, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Greater New York Joint Board, ACTWU, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  Textile Workers Pharmacy
- Maps- Hotel Directories, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Materials Available at 15th, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Plant Closings, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Labor Films, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Organizing, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- College Grants, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Labor Law Reform, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Textile Jacket, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  Ordering Blank
- Food Stamps, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Information Strikes, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Expense Sheets, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Vastina, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Car Rentals, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Membership Drive Leaflets, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Union Personnel, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Labor Law- George Meany Institute, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- J.P. Stevens Organizing Seminar, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  November 17,18
- Ropers Area, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Midwest Region, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Central Alabama Georgia Joint Board, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- J.P. Stevens, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  Allendale, South Carolina
- South Carolina Coastal Joint Board, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Vastina E. Wilson - Personal, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Georgia- Florida Leadership Conference, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Vastina - COPE School, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Withdrawal Locals 2398, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Vastina
- Central-Alabama Georgia Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Worth Textile and Brigadier
- Personal Check Stubs Receipts, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Local 2398, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Location: Johnsonville, South Carolina
- Tax Cut - Reagan's Budget, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Preparatory Material Steward, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Newsletter Mailing, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  June Convention
- Delegates List, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  schools
- Summer School, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous- School, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Upper South Regional Joint Board, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Local 254, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Clyde Bush
- Greater Northern Joint Board Local #150, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  Location: Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina
- Fieldcrest Arbitration, 1977-1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Delaware Valley Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Jacket Order Information- Order Blank, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Organizing, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Ohio State Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Homestead, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Jacket Order Information - Order Blanks, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  Clay
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  Textile Division
- J.P. Stevens Attendance ( Shop Steward Classes), 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  Locals 335 and 1771
- ACTWU- Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Labor Unity, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  Class Coverage
- Delaware Valley Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Local 189T, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Delaware Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  June 16-18
- Twin City Joint Board Newsletter, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Opperman, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  Local # 295T-1113T
- Scheduling Educational Activities, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- South Carolina Coastal Local 2398, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Correspondence Local 281, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  Bemis, Tennessee
- Local 281, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Indiana Kentucky Joint Board, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Central, South Jersey Joint Board, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Johnson and Johnson Conference, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  December 7-18
- Local 121 Cone, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  Reidsville, North Carolina
- Local # 1418, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  Chattanooga, Tennessee
- Local 1781, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  Charlotte, North Carolina
- Local 1867, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Local 1836, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Woon Socket, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Delaware Valley Joint Board, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Cowpens, South Carolina, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  Spartanburg, South Carolina ( Ramada Inn), November 14-16
- Scholarship Information, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Local 993,1137,2323, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Swedish Visitors, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Central Alabama- Georgia Joint Board, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  November 28-29; Hawkinsville, Georgia
- Jacket Orders- MVP Products, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- 9th Annual Summer School, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  July 7-13
- National School Power Manual, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- 15th Annual Summer School, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 14th National School, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 12th National School, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- 10th National School, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- 13th National School, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- 11th National School, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- 1st Annual Southern Summer School, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  June 19-23
- 4th Annual ACWA Southern School, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  October 4-8
- Mississippi Joint Board School, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  September 30 - October 4
- Mississippi Joint Board Conference, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  September 22-26
- 6th National School, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Florida Summer School, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  August 10-14
- North and South Carolina School, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  September 8-13
- ACWA Summer Schools, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- ACWA Southern School, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Southeastern Clothing Regional Joint Board
- Florida School, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- The Male Apparel Industries, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- The Third Annual Mississippi School, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  August 26-28
- Fourth Annual Mississippi Conference, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Fifth Annual Mississippi School, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  August 9-12
- Sixth Mississippi Educational Conference, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  August 8-11
- Seventh Annual Mississippi Educational Conference, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  August 13-16
- Legislative Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Eight Annual Mississippi Education Conference, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  September 23-26
- Mississippi Joint Board School, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  October 1-5
- Second Annual West Tennessee Education Conference, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  October 19-20
- Second Annual ACWA Southern School, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  October 7-11
- First New England Education Conference, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  January 25
- Education Conference, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Local 169, ACWA
- 1968 ACWA Summer Schools (Box 15, Folder 3)
- 1967 ACWA Schools (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Sixth Annual ACWA Midwestern Summer School, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  august 21-27
- A meeting "The Senator meets Amalgamated", 1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  May 12
- Southwest Summer School, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- ACWA Midwestern School, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  August 22-28
- ACWA Southwest Leadership Training Schools, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- ACWA Southwestern School, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  September 12-18
- ACWA Southwest Summer School, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  September 19-25
- ACWA Southern School, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Georgia Joint Board
- West Central Tennessee Joint Board School, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  October 2-5
- Georgia Joint Board School, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Legislative Conference, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  May 8
- ACWA Southern School, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Legislative Conferences, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Education Conference, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Georgia Joint Board Education Conference, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  February 9-10
- Second Tennessee Education Conference, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Education Conference, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  May 5-7
- ACWA Southern School, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- North and South Carolina, Virginia, Eastern Shore Area School, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- ACWA Eastern School, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  July 24-29
- ACWA Eastern School, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  July 25
- Sixteenth Annual National School, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  July 12-18
- ACWA Southern School, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Department of Education Manual, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- ACWA Southern School, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  South Alabama Joint Board
- ACWA Tennessee School, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Weekend Conference, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  December 5
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Pittsburgh Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Scranton Joint Board Education Conference, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  March 13
- Legislative News, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  April
- Southwest Regional Joint Board Legislative Conferences, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Southeast Clothing Regional Board School, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  September 21-26
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board Legislative Conferences, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board Conferences, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Weekend Institute, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  Local 1969
- Washington Legislative Institute, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- ACWA Washington Legislative Institute, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Education Conference, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Week-end Institute, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  ACWA, Local 169
- Midwest Regional Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board Legislative Conference, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board Conferences, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Education Conference, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  Local 796
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Pennsylvania Leadership Training Institute, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Weekend Conferences, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Local 346 Education Conferences, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  October 12
- Educational Series, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  Local 107 Eastern Shore Joint board
- First New England Education Conference, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board
- Labor Problems, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Textile Workers Union of America Summer School
- 27th Biennial Convention, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  ACWA General Executive Board Reports and Convention Proceedings
- Midwest Regional Leadership Conference, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  October 30
- Granite State Third Annual Leadership Conference, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  August 7-8
- Midwest Regional Leadership Conference, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  May 19-22
- Third Annual Ohio Statewide Conference, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  August 13-15
- Labor Education Service, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  West Virginia University
- COPE Activity Manual, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Textile Workers Union of America
- Textile Workers Union of America Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Workmen's Compensation Laws, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Maryland, Virginia and West Virginia
- Introduction to Social Security, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Congressional District Atlas, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census
- Grievance Arbitration Manual, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  Prepared by Phillips L. Garman; Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, University of Illinois
- The Philosophy of Socialist Education, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Author: L. Marcus
- The Corporate Ideology of American labor leaders from Gompers to Hillman, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Collective Bargaining on Welfare Plans, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper mill Workers
- COPE- Legislative Activity Manual, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Labor Problems, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Textile Workers Union Workers of America Summer School
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  contains: Progress Report 1974 and Program Activities for 1975
- Background on Collective Bargaining Issues, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers
- Department of Education, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America
- Explanation, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  AFL-CIO
- College Education Financing, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Leadership Training Manual, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- A Teaching Guide for AFL-CIO Stewards, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Instructions and suggestions for a 6-session course
- Indiana- Kentucky Third Annual Leadership Conference, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  October 1-2
- Orientation Kit for J.P. Stevens Campaign ( Folder 1: ACTWU), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Orientation Kit for J.P. Stevens (Folder 2: The Industry), 1968-1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  TWUA research:1968 Earnings Gap: June 1975
- Orientation Kit for J.P. Stevens ( Folder 3: Unionism), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Orientation Kit for J.P. Stevens (folder 4: J.P. Stevens), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Orientation Kit for J.P. Stevens (Folder 5: Support for Stevens workers) (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Steward Manual (Folder 1), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Steward Manual (Folder 2), 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Steward Manual (Folder 3), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Steward Manual (Folder 4), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Labor History Documents (Volume I), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Labor History Documents (Volume II), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Labor History Documents (Volume III), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Legal Aspects of Collective Bargaining, Agreements, Organizing, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Staff Training, Spring
- Day Care: Resources for Decisions, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- New York State Official Directory: Union Made Products and Services, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Thirteenth edition
- A Teaching Guide on How to Run a Union Meeting, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  publication No. 81
- Union Leadership Program, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Indiana University Labor and research Center
- Labor and the Schools: A Conference Report, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  September 25-27
- UAW-CAP Training Sessions on Campaign Techniques, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Defend your Dollar Study Forum, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Communications Workers of America Education Department
- CIO Education Manual, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  volume I
- C.O.P.E, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- COPE Materials, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board Washington Conference, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  May 21-23
- Washington Reports UAW, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Auto Safety, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Harvest of Shame, 1961-1966 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Leisure wear Conference, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  April 23
- Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Memos- Educational Department, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- U.S. Labor Department (Informational Statistics), 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Trades and Jobs Legislative Newsletter, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Consumer Protection, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Union Label Explanation, 1948-1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Organizing, 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Convention 1966 Speeches, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Legislative Material, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Coordinators Manual, 1962-1969 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Publications 2, 1953-1957 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Social Security Improvements- Outline and Materials #1, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Debate Kits, 1958-1963 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Scholarship Program, 1958-1963 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Textile Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- United Auto workers (UAW) AFL-CIO, 1953-1966 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Social Insurance and Unemployment Insurance (Federal and State), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- United Steel Workers, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Publications #1, 1964-1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Taxes, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Taxes - Increase/ Loopholes, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Taxes Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Scranton, PA, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Junior High School Information, 1964-1968 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- COPE-WAD Work-book, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- West Virginia, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- New Members Information, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Improvements-Social Security Law, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Film Discussion Guides, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- New York State- AFL-CIO Literature, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Seminar on Teaching Techniques, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Education Program for Joint Boards and Locals: Awarding Scholarships, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- outlines, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Local 189 notes, 1966-1970 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Plants and Profits, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  May
- Poverty-Welfare, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 20)